Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand!
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights?
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day!
And the values we had were about to
collapse Oh just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone.
We'll go where we all wanna go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
I am waiting for you, Momonosuke.
I am waiting for your order.
Far have I traveled to stand beside you.
Now in your moment of need,
I will fight in your name.
I was able to speak with
Zunisha for a moment at least.
So you can talk to the elephant.
Odin predicted this years ago.
You're everything he dreamed you would be.
You've got this!
And you'll lead this world to a new dawn!
We're still missing the most
important piece of this puzzle.
After reading Father's journal, I understand
that I must survive no matter what.
But I'm still lost.
Because he tore out the most
important page before I could see it!
Laugh Tale.
The final island.
What did Father and Roger see there?
What made them laugh?
I struggle to understand my mission.
Father was not a prophet.
If he were here now,
would he still insist on opening
the borders like he did before?
I have not the wisdom to solve this.
If opening the borders puts
the people of Wano in danger,
then I do not want to do it!
Am I a coward, Yamato?
Tell me!
Charret, get inside the dome!
We have taken our revenge, but I fear
the battle for Wano is far from over.
Hey!
I'm ready!
Let's go help out!
Seems this island can
collapse at any moment.
We had better hurry them.
I got you, bro!
Hold on!
Really put your life on the line.
It's getting roughed up, aren't ya?
Stay steady!
I'm gonna reel ya in!
Hey!
You're still alive, right?
Say something!
You better not be dead, bro!
Zoro!
I won't let you die.
You gotta stay with me.
This is bad, really bad.
The whole castle is about to collapse.
Hamlet, get us to the exit and hurry!
No need to worry, I will!
Not to pressure you, but lives
are hanging in the balance.
If there's ever been a time
to deliver, this is it!
The time has come.
For even ninja like you and I To be free!
The fiery battle in the third-floor
hallway has come to an end.
The winner, Race of the Mist.
Are you a samurai?
You need to get out of here now.
You're a Gourmet of Sir
Luffy's, aren't you?
Let me aid you.
You're in no shape to fight, I fear.
You have done enough.
I must try.
I can't rest till the battle is won.
I won't let you march to your own death.
Then I need a favor.
Finger Pistol?
Shift. Shake!
Finger pistol!
You have to live!
Kiku!
Impossible.
Maha!
Was this your plan, Izo?
You were going to sacrifice
yourself from the start.
Why would a leftover from the Whitebeard
Pirates want to help those brats?
I must find Nico Robin quickly.
I don't have time to
deal with this right now.
Listen carefully.
It's an Imperial command
from the Five Elders.
What?
From the Five Elders?
They said, erase Straw
Hat Luffy immediately.
Do you realize what you're asking of me?
Straw Hat is fighting
an emperor right now.
You expect me just to step into
the middle of Kaido's fight?
That'll never work.
Then make it work.
It's the only option.
The longer Straw Hat fights someone
of his caliber, the greater the risk.
Don't you get it?
The five elders call it
a necessary precaution.
If they're worried about it,
then we know the rumors are true.
At the very least, we don't want
to find out, understand? I'll wait.
I can't die yet.
I've accomplished nothing.
What's going on with that crew?
What makes the Straw Hats so special?
Oh, Mathieu, thank you so much
for doing such a wonderful job.
You did it, boss!
Captain!
You did it from the sea!
This is a big deal, a really big deal!
Sounds like Big Mom won't be coming back.
It's hard to believe.
Mama, no!
What are you crying about, Zeus?
You don't need Big Mom anymore
now that you've got me, right?
Of course not, Ami!
Master, here!
Stay close to me!
Looks like we can't relax just yet.
We have to be ready for anything.
This island is a bomb set to explode.
Luffy I hope you can wrap this up soon.
Why aren't you here?
Fukurokuju!
Oh,
Kurosaki don't worry my dear we'll get
out of this accursed place soon enough
useless ninja you're supposed to be
helping me so what's the hold up huh that
bastard didn't run away on his own did
he a ninja must serve his Lord till the
end if anyone's gonna die it should be him
wonder who caused
that quake conjurer oh
Maybe.
I sure hope there's not more on the way.
Hey!
That's enough!
We're in danger!
Why are you playing music
at a time like this?
Are you listening to me?
Stop this instant!
Do you realize we're both
dead if we don't get help?
And here you are wearing
that ridiculous mask.
You haven't shown me
your face once have you?
Take off that mask right now!
You are Kurosaki, right?
You have to be.
Please say something.
Are you a ghost?
Oh.
Let's go.
Stop!
Have you noticed yet? Hey!
Those little bastards.
They really did it.
No!
She's gone now!
I'm in this way!
Jackie and Traffy won?
Wow, that's awesome!
Should we get ready, Kaido might come.
That would be pointless.
Just hope it's Luffy
who comes back for us.
My energy is all spent.
I gave this everything I had.
I can't fight anymore.
Mama, mama.
Hey, brat!
You know it's rude to stare!
Hello?
You got a mouth, don't you?
How old are you, mama? mama!
15.
So young.
This must be your first
time teaming up with rocks!
Well, there's never a dull moment.
I'll warn you, rocks
is a good for nothing.
You can't trust a word he says.
You got a problem?
You bring it to me, mama! mama!
The name's linlin and don't you forget it.
I'm gonna be king of these seas.
Welcome to the team!
Looking back,
you and I have known each other
an awfully long time, haven't we?
You old hack!
It's not fair!
Why does that have to happen now?
We made a promise together.
We were gonna get the one piece!
Fourth gear.
I have a moment of silence.
This is a very emotional time for me.
Read the damn room.
I can't move.
I'm trapped here.
How careless of you.
You got so worked up that
you didn't even notice.
Gomorrah Saki, why aren't you helping?
Get this damn rubble off of me.
Something is wrong.
I feel so weak.
Why can't I transform?
Of course you can't.
I couldn't have you using your power,
after all, so I stuck a sea prism
stone nail in you, to keep you docile.
But why?
None of this makes any sense.
We were going to escape together.
You mean you don't love me anymore?
Anymore?
How amusing.
I never loved you in the first place.
It's quite a coincidence that
you like this piece so much.
It's called Moon Princess.
That's beautiful, Hiyori.
You've gotten so good at playing. Really?
The song's called Moon Princess
I'm gonna try to get even better.
Good, keep it up!
You can play it at my funeral someday.
Hey momo, stop making your sister cry!
You're the one who made her cry.
Me, the funeral thing, I'm
sorry, it was only a joke.
Promise?
Like I die and leave you.
My father loved this song as well.
How peculiar that you would have
the same taste as Kozuki Oden.
And now, every time I play it,
I remember my father's face.
Your father?
Knowing that, even as I avenge his
death, I dare not show a smile.
Not in front of you!
Captain!
Hydra!
I don't give a crap what
you guys had planned.
The people of this country are starving.
You've taken enough from them.
I'm giving this fourth gear
everything that I have left.
And I won't stop attacking
till I put an end to you.
I can't tell what his
attempts are coming from.
You're leaving this country!
I'll make sure of it!
Wano doesn't need you!
I'm kicking you out!